there you
там здесь
smile
лыбишься
who
которые
didn’t participate yourself, we
не участвовали себя
participate in all this is your image of a Russian
участвуем во все это ваш образ русского
tank,
танка это
I go out once on Friday, well, that is, I have
я выхожу раз в пятницу ну то есть у меня
such an opportunity here on Friday to
такая возможность есть вот в пятницу на
Saturday, everything is family work there, and here I
субботу все там семья работа и вот я тут
go out and don’t shoot anything, it just
выхожу и ничего не снимаю просто
tears it off,
отрывает
well  as if yes, that is, I don’t have any of these, I
ну как бы да то есть никаких этих у меня
need friends here, Lucy is lying there,
надо тут лежат друзья там люси лежит
Masha has already died, then everyone here was
маша уже сдохла ушла потом все тут были
shorter, so
короче ну и
I’m trying to make fun, well, how can we
вот пытаюсь прикалываться ну как у нас
make fun, well, as if there were no object of
посмешить ну как бы никакого предмета
negativity so that there weren’t and
негатива чтобы не было а
you yourself are from the
вы сами откуда
Tambov of Russia  barn I'm from ukraine city of
тамбов россии амбар я из украины город
police but look i'm scary on the street how
милиции а вот смотри я улице страшно как
do you feel about the van in ukraine
вы относитесь к ване в украине
which one takes place in ukraine and
какая которой проходит в украине а
who declared war on whom and what does the
кто кому объявил войну а причем тут
announcement have to do with if for example some
объявления если например вас какой-то
dude comes and starts hitting you with varnish on the
чувак придёт и начнёт бить душ лаком по
head there
голове
will be a fight  without declaring a fight,
будет драка без объявления драки
there will be no mutual aggression, that is, if
не будет обоюдной агрессия то есть если
when they beat 1 if they just beat you, it’s not
когда бьют 1 если просто вас бьют это не
flaws
огрехи
wait wait and no one will think
подождите подождите а никто не подумать
why this dude was beaten  there
почему этого чувака начали бить по
can also be harmony on the head and the
голове может быть тоже стройность и
dude never started to be beaten, the one
никогда чувака начали бить виноват тот
who started to beat like you is
кто начал бить как вы
not true, first the person must
не правда сначала человек должен
violate the rules of the game and then they already
нарушать правила игры а потом его уже
beat him not just so that you walk down the street
бьют не просто так что идешь по улице
tell us, for example, where in the
тебе на нас расскажите например где в
criminal code it allows you to beat a
криминальном кодексе разрешает бить
person  at times, the code
человека за какапо временами кодексе
is not allowed to beat anything at all
вообще ничего не разрешено бить не так
, or somewhere in VKontakte sheets, you can
вот или где-то во вконтакте листов можно
beat a person
бить человека
who
который
did something there for what, for example, in
что-то там сделал вот за что например в
which case it is possible to beat, but can I
каком случае возможно бить а можно я
give you questions about cancer, let's
приведу вопросы рак давайте
see if we are in Mexico  now
смотри если бы мы в мексику сейчас
they’d come, they’d put their troops, what
приехали поставили бы свои войска как
do you think, the americans went to war
думаешь американцы пошли войной
no
нет
where you can’t keep nuclear weapons
где нельзя содержать ядерное оружие
shan
шанский
some
какие-то
subscriptions for a long time it’s completely different
подписки долго это совсем другое это
he
посмотрите ему интервью и что то что он
said and when in the colony we
сказал и когда в колонии а мы нам
will violate the
нарушим бит
Budapest memorandum and deploy
будапештский меморандум и разместим
nuclear weapons
ядерное оружие
you can now find it right now because it
можете сейчас найти прямо потому что это
has been told to you more than once it has not been said more
уже не раз говорят вам так не говорилось
than once you know that according to the Budapest
не раз знаете что по будапештскому
memorandum of Russia, for example, it was the
меморандуму россии например было
guarantor of the
гарантом
Budapest memorandum to actually
будапештский меморандум фактически
read and waste your time and the
читать и тратить свое время и
Budapest memorandum does not
будапештский меморандум не действует
actually work in 2014 when Russia attacked
фактически 2014 года когда россия напала
Ukraine
на украину
on February 4
с 4 февраля
not February 26,
не 26 февраля
look at the Russian soldiers what all of
посмотрите российские солдаты чего все
ours
наши вас
asked you answers look I want why you do
спросили отвечает смотрите хочу почему у
n’t want to tell harming I don’t want to
не хотите рассказать вредя я не хочу
talk years donbass who hammered from
разговаривать лет донбасс кто долбил с
russia started a war in the donbass my in
россия начала войну на донбассе мои в
their inhabitants of the donbass but also the inhabitants of the
своих жителей донбасса но и жители
donbass then the inhabitants of ukraine
донбасса то жители украины
that the inhabitants
что жители
after when they weren’t asked about them when she
после когда об их не спросили когда она
tell me when they disconnect the date to
скажите когда они отсоедините дату
name I’m already tired of talking about it
назвать я уже устал об этом разговор они
and you can give it by dates I
и давать вы сможете по датам вот четко я
’m telling you clearly on February 26, 2014 the
вам говорю 26 февраля 2014 года
Russian military captured the Crimean parliament,
захватили парламент крыма российские
this began the Russian
военные с этого началась российские
battles in Ukraine in the Donbass  12
сражений в украину на донбассе 12
determined
определяются
captured the city of Slavs  to Russian
захватили город славянск российские
militants led by Girkin,
боевики под предводительством гиркина с
this was the start of hostilities before
этого и начались военные действия до
that, no one bombed the Donbass
этого никто никакой донбасс не бомбил
with seriousness until you can tell me
уже серьезностью до можете мне сказать
someone who died before that until the date of
кто-то погибший до этого до даты 12
April 12 someone in the Donbass died attack
апреля кто-то на донбассе погиб атаку
arrogantly years 2000
заносчиво лет 2000
2009 8 years ago  April 12, the
2009 году 8 лет назад 12 апреля
peak
пик
man colander so started approved to
человек дуршлаг так начиналась одобрен
help and their colander on the head yes
помочь и их дуршлагом на голове да
tells man now you or the
рассказывает man вот теперь ты или
head and before these call
головы и до этих называть
him and tell 8 years bombed everyone against
он и рассказывать 8 лет бомбили все на
whom you read against you clearly by dates
кого почитаешь противо ты четко по датам
in chronology so we peak their mountain and
по хронологии так мы их пик гора и
start  how the hell can we know to
начинаете как чу му шу можно знаем
play with sharks income dope theft
играться с акулами доходом дурман theft
ag on ithaca clowns bins slide more
ag на итаке клоуны урны слайд пуще
normative and russia cheese zmieva i’m sacred
нормативным а россия сыр змиева я свято
not ukraine and russia doesn’t mean
не украина и россия на разумеет
abundance attacked ukraine and wine in the
обильность напала на украину и вина на
donbass you are going on the trail of russian
донбассе ты едешь на следок российской
aggression taiga part on russian
агрессии тайге части на российской
aggression in ukraine
агрессии в украине
food at all carve repeated no one
еду у все высечь повторными никто
kitchen was no one on and was evil and
кухонных бывал никто на и был злым и
poland the jew was there laws where it would be
польши иудейке было там законы где это
Yes, and David has Russian militants, well,
было и у давида российские боевики ну
let Rome tell the truth in the oily very sight of the
пошли рима правду в масляный саму виду
cattle said Ross is everywhere this is 100 watts and
[__] сказал росс повсюду это 100 вт и
comments put likes write to the senator we
коменты ставте лайки пишыте сенатором мы
mail.ru xtc informative front puff
mail.ru хтц информативный фронт затяжку
lacma thickets in ukraine
lacma зарослях по украине